Rahul Nayak

Jalandhar, Punjab, India



nayakrahul2001@gmail.com



8847806936



linkedin.com/in/bollyrahul

Summary

A 19-Year old Filmmaker and a writer to the core, Rahul is an inventive storyteller, who travels across the planet in search of stories and moments that don't necessarily be inventive but are pure to the roots.

He also loves his work and is always honest about his work culture.

Experience



Chief Operational Officer

Griffin LPU

Jun 2021 - Present (6 months +)



Content Writer

Lovely Professional University Sep 2019 - Present (2 years 3 months +)

Video Editor

Lovely Professional University Alumni Association Oct 2020 - Present (1 year 2 months +)

Founder

Life Like That
Dec 2018 - Present (3 years +)
Founder Of Life Like That!

Founder

ASPDIT FILMS

May 2017 - Present (4 years 7 months +) Founder of ASPDIT.

Campus Ambassador

Josh Talks

Feb 2021 - Mar 2021 (2 months)

BCORD Campus Ambassador

Board Infinity

Dec 2020 - Feb 2021 (3 months)

Campus Ambassador

Aakar IIT Bombay Mar 2020 - Sep 2020 (7 months)

Campus Ambassador

Aakriti techfest Mar 2020 - Mar 2020 (1 month)

Campus Ambassador

TATVA DTU Mar 2020 - Mar 2020 (1 month)

YOUTHURE Video Editor

YouthVibe: LPU's Open Global Fest Jan 2020 - Feb 2020 (2 months)

Education

Lovely Professional University

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, cse 2019 - 2023

M ODM Public School

+2 Higher Education, Science (CSE) 2017 - 2019

DAV Public School

Class 10, Science 2011 - 2017

Licenses & Certifications

Cerificate Of Achievement - Silverzone foundation

TIML and CSS for Beginners-Build a Website & Launch Online - Udemy UC-2bab4211-4bbb-414c-b183-6440d2438e6a

Google Analytics for Beginners - Google Analytics Academy Issued Mar 2020 - Expires Mar 2023

Fundamentals of Digital Marketing - Google Digital Gara

B5D VRD DSN

- Advanced Google Analytics Google Analytics Academy Issued Mar 2020 Expires Mar 2023
- Twitter Flight School Video Badge Twitter Issued Mar 2020 Expires Mar 2021 128179368
- Embracing Change Harappa Education
- Photography Foundations: Mobile Photography LinkedIn
- Tim VFX for Architectural Visualization LinkedIn
- Creating a Short Film: 09 VFX Environments LinkedIn
- Learning Video Production and Editing LinkedIn
- Time Video Pre-production for Low-Budget Films LinkedIn
- in Voice-Over for Video and Animation LinkedIn
- Complete Guide For Effective Business Communication Eduonix Learning Solutions Pvt Ltd
- After Effects: Advanced Compositing Tracking and Roto Techniques LinkedIn
- **in** Advanced Cinematic Video Lighting LinkedIn
- in Creating Online Video with Android Phones LinkedIn
- in HTML5: File API LinkedIn
- Tim HTML5: Geolocation LinkedIn
- in Cinematic Video Lighting LinkedIn

- Corporate and Documentary Video Lighting LinkedIn
- Time Video Product Lighting Techniques LinkedIn
- in Lighting a Video Interview LinkedIn
- in Improve Your Lighting Skills LinkedIn
- in Lighting Design for Video Productions LinkedIn
- in Advanced Photoshop: Lookup Tables and Gradient Maps LinkedIn
- REAKTOR: Advanced Instruments and Effects LinkedIn
- **Mriting Articles** LinkedIn
- Graphic Design Careers: First Steps LinkedIn
- Running a Video Production Business LinkedIn
- Camera Movement for Video Productions LinkedIn
- Learning Cinematography: 1 Narrative Fundamentals LinkedIn
- **In Learning Cinematography: 3 Hands On Techniques** LinkedIn
- **In Learning Cinematography: 2 Working on Set** LinkedIn
- in HTML: Tables LinkedIn
- in HTML Essential Training LinkedIn
- Succeeding in Web Development: Full Stack and Front End LinkedIn
- Responsive Layout LinkedIn

- in HTML & CSS: Creating Forms LinkedIn
- **Meb Programming Foundations** LinkedIn
- Programming Foundations: Fundamentals LinkedIn
- TIN UX Foundations: Accessibility LinkedIn
- in User Experience for Web Design LinkedIn
- in CSS Essential Training LinkedIn
- in Learning GitHub LinkedIn
- Crisis Communication LinkedIn
- in JavaScript Essential Training LinkedIn
- The Learning React.js LinkedIn
- Sass Essential Training LinkedIn
- Bootstrap 4 Essential Training LinkedIn
- **Become a Front-End Web Developer** LinkedIn
- in Introduction to Photography LinkedIn
- in Being an Effective Team Member LinkedIn
- in Communication Foundations LinkedIn
- Social Media Marketing Foundations LinkedIn
- Social Media Marketing: Managing Online Communities LinkedIn

- Social Media Marketing for Small Business LinkedIn
- Social Media Marketing with Facebook and Twitter LinkedIn
- Marketing on Snapchat LinkedIn
- Marketing on Facebook LinkedIn
- Advertising on Facebook LinkedIn
- in Advertising on Instagram LinkedIn
- Advertising on YouTube LinkedIn
- Marketing on Twitter LinkedIn
- in Social Media Marketing: ROI LinkedIn
- Time Video Foundations: Cameras and Shooting LinkedIn
- **in** Creating a Short Film: 07 Cinematography LinkedIn
- Become a Social Media Marketer LinkedIn
- Introduction to Virtual Reality Coursera
- The History of Film and Video Editing LinkedIn
- **EF SET Certificate** EF Standard English Test (EF SET)
- Foundations of Video: The Art of Editing LinkedIn
- in Introduction to Video Editing LinkedIn
- Premiere Pro CC 2019 Essential Training: The Basics LinkedIn

- Final Cut Pro X 10.4.4 Essential Training LinkedIn
- Introduction to Video Dialogue Editing LinkedIn
- Introduction to Video Color Correction LinkedIn
- Become a Video Editor LinkedIn
- Make the Move from Individual Contributor to Manager LinkedIn
- in New Manager Foundations LinkedIn
- in Onboarding New Hires as a Manager LinkedIn
- Delegating Tasks LinkedIn
- **Online Marketing Foundations** LinkedIn
- Business Storytelling with C.C. Chapman LinkedIn
- Building an Integrated Online Marketing Plan LinkedIn
- Tim UX Foundations: Content Strategy LinkedIn
- SEO Foundations LinkedIn
- in Content Marketing: Blogs LinkedIn
- in Learning to Write Marketing Copy LinkedIn
- in Become a Manager LinkedIn
- **in** Content Marketing: Staying Relevant LinkedIn
- **in** Content Marketing Foundations LinkedIn

- Coaching and Developing Employees LinkedIn
- Performance Management: Setting Goals and Managing Performance LinkedIn
- in Google Analytics Essential Training LinkedIn
- Produce Audio for Film and Video Projects LinkedIn
- in Audio for Video: Production and Post Sound Techniques LinkedIn
- Tim Video Gear: Audio LinkedIn
- Audio for Video: 3 Real World Solutions LinkedIn
- Audio for Video: 2 Tips & Techniques LinkedIn

Skills

```
Video Editing • Leadership • Videography • Video Production • Video Post-Production • Film Production • Digital Media • Compositing • Architectural Design • Digital Marketing
```

Honors & Awards

Best Story Award - We Feel Creations

Oct 2020

Our Film, 'Call of Illusions' won the award for Best Story at 2nd We Feel Special Award International Short Film Festival 2020.